Guide to the Roe Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Indians at work; Courtship; Families; Indians of Central America -- Missions; Indians of Mexico -- Missions; Indians of North America -- Missions; Indians of South America -- Missions; Indians -- Missions; Marriage; Missionaries -- Biography; Missionaries -- Correspondence; Missions -- United States; Women missionaries; Women -- Education; New York (State) -- Social life and customs; Oklahoma -- History; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Religious aspects; West (U.S.); Diaries; Photographs; Sermons; Authors; Clergy; Educators; Engineers; Missionaries; Women teachers; Caldwell, Susan Elizabeth Roe, 1826-1907; Caldwell, Wilhelmina, 1860-1945; Cloud, Elizabeth Georgian Bender; Cloud, Henry Roe, 1885-1950; Collier, John, 1884-1968; Colony Mission (Colony, Okla.); Cox, Samuel H. (Samuel Hanson), 1793-1880; Crosby, Howard, 1826-1891; Harris, Elizabeth Merwin Page, 1889-1969; Landon, Caroline Powell Roe, 1859-1897; Leupp, Francis E. (Francis Ellington), 1849-1918; Meengs, Joanna, 1883-1927; Merwin, Alexander Moss, 1839-1905; Merwin, Miranda B., d. 1925; Page, Elizabeth Merwin Roe, 1861-1943; Page, Elizabeth, 1889-; Porter Eleazar, 1806-1886; Porter, Jonathan Edwards, 1815-1896; Porter, Moses, 1768-1854; Quinan, Henry Wickham, 1864-; Roe, Alfred Cox, 1823-; Roe, Caroline Marsh, 1865-1948; Roe, Caroline Mathilda Clark, 1830-1893; Roe, Edward Payson, 1838-1888; Roe, Emma Wickham, 1832-1906; Roe, James Gilbert, 1825-1907; Roe, John Peter, 1834-1909; Roe, Joseph Wickham, 1871-; Roe, Mary A. (Mary Abigail), approximately 1840-; Roe, Mary Sherwood Lambertson, 1872-1960; Roe, Mary Wickham, 1863-1941; Roe, Nellie Allen, 1876-1903; Roe, Walter C., 1860-1913; Roe, William Edgar, 1857-1934; Schauffler, Marjorie Page, 1897-1983; Seger, John H. (John Homer), 1846-1928; Snell, Moses Porter, 1839-1909; Stebbins, Esther Wickham, 1802-1854; Watermulder, Gustavus Adolphus, 1873-1946; Wickham, Abigail, 1809-1872; Wright, Frank Hall, 1860-1922; Page family; Rowe family; United States. Bureau of Indian Affairs; American Indian Institute (Wichita, Kan.); Amherst College -- Students; Reformed Church in America; Roe Indian Institute (Wichita, Kan.); Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1895; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1910; Yale University -- Students
- Family Correspondence, 1832-1960; Series I; 6.25' (15 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Series I, FAMILY CORRESPONDENCE, fills Boxes 1-15 of the Roe Family Papers. The series is chronologically arranged. Undated correspondence is found in Boxes 14-15, folders 420-463.
  - Correspondence, 1832-1857 October (Box 1, Folder 1-33)
  - Correspondence, 1857 November-1864 July (Box 2, Folder 34-75)
  - Correspondence, 1864 August-1866 July (Box 3, Folder 76-102)
  - Correspondence, 1866 October-1883 June (Box 4, Folder 103-138)
  - Correspondence, 1883 July-1886 May (Box 5, Folder 139-168)
  - Correspondence, 1886 June-1889 April (Box 6, Folder 169-201)
  - Correspondence, 1889 May-1895 April (Box 7, Folder 202-229)
  - Correspondence, 1895 May-1900 (Box 8, Folder 230-265)
  - Correspondence, 1901-1907 (Box 9, Folder 266-298)
  - Correspondence, 1908-1923 (Box 10, Folder 299-333)
  - Correspondence, 1924-1940 September (Box 11, Folder 334-365)
  - Correspondence, 1940 October-1958 June (Box 12, Folder 366-392)
  - Correspondence, 1958 July-1960 June (Box 13, Folder 393-416)
  - Correspondence, 1960 July-1960 November (Box 14, Folder 417-419)
    General note
    See also: box 156, folders 1-22
  - Page, Elizabeth Merwin Roe, undated (Box 14, Folder 420-441)
  - Page, Elizabeth Merwin Roe, undated (Box 15, Folder 442-452)
  - Roe, Joseph Wickham, undated (Box 15, Folder 453)
  - Roe, Mary Wickham, undated (Box 15, Folder 454-455)
  - B - P, undated (Box 15, Folder 456)
  - R - W, undated (Box 15, Folder 457)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 15, Folder 458-459)
  - Fragments, undated (Box 15, Folder 46o-463)
- Family Papers, 1846-1977; Series II; 6.0' (14 boxes)
  Series II, FAMILY PAPERS, is located in Boxes 16-29 of the Roe Family Papers. The material is arranged alphabetically by person or family and then chronologically.
  - Brewster family genealogy, undated (Box 16, Folder 464)
  - Dresser family genealogy, undated (Box 16, Folder 465)
  - Edwards and Williams families: genealogy, undated (Box 16, Folder 466)
  - Landon, Caroline Powell Roe
    - Estate papers, 1897, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 467)
    - Magazine clippings, undated (Box 16, Folder 468)
    - Obituaries, 1897 (Box 16, Folder 469)
    - Sermons and sermon notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 470)
  - Ludlow family genealogy, 1914, 1939, undated (Box 16, Folder 471-472)
  - Merwin family
    - Reminiscences, undated (Box 16, Folder 473)
    - Scrapbook, undated (Box 16, Folder 474)
  - Merwin, Miranda B: guestbook, undated (Box 16, Folder 475)
    See also: box 157, folder 23
  - Roe family
    - Address book, undated (Box 16, Folder 476)
    - Genealogy, undated (Box 16, Folder 477-480)
    - Memorabilia
      - American flags, undated (Box 17, Folder 481)
      - Basketwork, undated (Box 17, Folder 482-483)
      - Civil War chaplain's cap and stripes, 1864 (Box 17, Folder 484)
      - Drawing of girl, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 485)
      - Hair, undated (Box 17, Folder 486)
      - Leaf, pouch, tile, undated (Box 17, Folder 487)
    - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 17, Folder 488)
    - Papers, undated (Box 17, Folder 489-490)
    - Pouch with newspaper clippings, 1870, undated (Box 17, Folder 491)
    - "Recollections of the Roe family", undated (Box 17, Folder 492)
    - Surveyor's book, undated (Box 17, Folder 493)
  - Roe, Alfred Cox
    See also: box 114, folder 1968
    - Addresses and lectures, 1870-1875, undated (Box 18, Folder 494-495)
    - American Christian Commission: notes and reports, 1865-1867 (Box 18, Folder 496)
    - Bills, 1891-1893 (Box 18, Folder 497-500)
    - Check stubs, 1897-1900, undated (Box 18, Folder 501)
    - Civil War
      - Chaplain's record books, 1864-1865 (Box 18, Folder 502)
      - Chaplain's reports, 1864-1865 (Box 18, Folder 503)
      - Chaplain's roster, 1865 (Box 18, Folder 504)
      - Enlistment and discharge papers, 1863-1865 (Box 18, Folder 505)
      - Evangelical Christian Union, undated (Box 18, Folder 506)
      - Orders, 1864-1865 (Box 18, Folder 507)
      - Writings, 1864-1888, undated (Box 18, Folder 508-510)
    - Funeral addresses, 1870-1877 (Box 19, Folder 511)
    - Lecture notes, 1880's (Box 19, Folder 512)
    - Memorabilia, printed, undated (Box 19, Folder 513)
    - Memorabilia of trip to Scotland, 1890 (Box 19, Folder 514)
    - Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 19, Folder 515)
    - New York Collegiate Institute, 1901 (Box 19, Folder 516)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1858-1900 (Box 19, Folder 517-518)
    - Prayer meeting skeletons, 1873-1877 (Box 19, Folder 519-520)
    - Register of sermons, baptisms, etc., 1870-1882 (Box 19, Folder 521)
    - "Street Talks", 1870-1871 (Box 19, Folder 522)
    - Writings, 1868-1881 (Box 19, Folder 523-528)
    - Writings, 1884, 1890 (Box 20, Folder 529)
    - Writings: "The Duty of Being Beautiful", undated (Box 20, Folder 530)
    - Writings: "Hawthorne and his Teachings", undated (Box 20, Folder 531)
  - Roe, Caroline Marsh: scrapbook of the Rockies, 1915 (Box 20, Folder 532)
  - Roe, Edward Payson
    - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 20, Folder 533)
    - Scrapbook of reviews, undated (Box 20, Folder 534-535)
    - Writings: "Doing Better" and "Elder Strong Speaks Rather Strongly", 1885, undated (Box 20, Folder 536)
  - Roe, Emma Wickham
    - Accounts and bills, 1900-1906 (Box 20, Folder 537)
    - Composition book and notebook, 1846, undated (Box 20, Folder 538)
    - Estate papers, 1906-1908 (Box 20, Folder 539)
    - Memorabilia and obituary, 1880-1906 (Box 20, Folder 540)
    - Papers relating to S.F.B. Morse, 1856, 1870, undated (Box 20, Folder 541)
  - Roe, James Gilbert
    - Financial records, 1880-1888 (Box 20, Folder 542)
    - Memorial poems and obituary, 1897 (Box 20, Folder 543)
  - Roe, Joseph Wickham
    See also: box 114, folders 1969-1970
    See also: boxes 158-160, folder 35
    - Account books and compositions, 1881-1883, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 544)
    - Address: "Ludlow genealogy", 1938 (Box 21, Folder 545)
    - Estate papers, 1959-1977 (Box 21, Folder 546-548)
    - Fairfield News, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 549)
    - Funeral service, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 550)
    - Membership certificates, 1925, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 551)
    - Middlebury College, honorary degree, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 552)
    - Newspaper clippings and obituaries, 1874-1960 (Box 21, Folder 553)
    - Pamphlet on Memorial Quadrangle, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 554)
    - Programs, 1889-1895 (Box 21, Folder 555)
    - School reports, Hill School, 1886-1887 (Box 21, Folder 556)
    - Wedding invitation, 1902 (Box 21, Folder 557)
    - Zeppelin papers, undated (Box 21, Folder 558)
  - Roe, Mary Abigail
    See also: box 114, folders 1971-1972
    - Autograph album, 1850's (Box 21, Folder 559)
    - Bills, 1904-1909 (Box 21, Folder 560-561)
    - Calendar of Maud Hoffman: "The Face of a Friend", 1899 (Box 21, Folder 562)
    - "Feathered Tenants of a California Ranch", undated (Box 21, Folder 563)
    - Floral catalogues, 1889-1909 (Box 21, Folder 564)
    - Greeting cards and visiting cards, undated (Box 21, Folder 565)
    - Illustrations: ancient ruins, undated (Box 21, Folder 566)
    - Illustrations: art, undated (Box 22, Folder 567)
    - Knitting instructions and recipes, undated (Box 22, Folder 568)
    - Lectures
      - Assyria, undated (Box 22, Folder 569)
      - Assyria and Babylonia, undated (Box 22, Folder 570)
      - Egypt, undated (Box 22, Folder 571)
      - Greece, undated (Box 22, Folder 572)
      - India, undated (Box 22, Folder 573)
      - Macedonia, undated (Box 22, Folder 574)
      - Persian Empire, undated (Box 22, Folder 575)
      - Rome, undated (Box 22, Folder 576-578)
      - "Roundtable Talks", undated (Box 22, Folder 579)
    - Literary fragments, undated (Box 22, Folder 580)
    - Merwin, A. Moss: "The Drift from Rome" and obituary, 1901, undated (Box 22, Folder 581)
    - "Monday Club" programs, 1900-1905 (Box 22, Folder 582)
    - Natural science
      - Birds, undated (Box 23, Folder 583-585)
      - Botanical illustrations, undated (Box 23, Folder 586)
      - Botanical specimens, undated (Box 23, Folder 587-588)
      - Botany: field guides, undated (Box 23, Folder 589)
      - Evolution, undated (Box 23, Folder 590)
      - Insects, undated (Box 23, Folder 591-592)
      - Mammals, marine invertebrates, and minerals, undated (Box 23, Folder 593)
    - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 23, Folder 594)
    - Notebooks
      - Ancient history; China, undated (Box 23, Folder 595)
      - Helen Hunt Jackson; mineralogy, undated (Box 23, Folder 596)
      - Mineralogy, undated (Box 23, Folder 597)
      - Natural history, undated (Box 24, Folder 598)
      - Physiology; War of 1812, undated (Box 24, Folder 599)
      - Sea-shells, undated (Box 24, Folder 600)
      - Zoology, undated (Box 24, Folder 601)
      - Zoology; astronomy; U.S. history, undated (Box 24, Folder 602)
    - Obituary, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 603)
    - Pamphlets, religious, undated (Box 24, Folder 604)
    - Plaque, undated (Box 24, Folder 605)
    - Plate for visiting card, undated (Box 24, Folder 606)
    - "Recollections of the Roe family", undated (Box 24, Folder 607)
    - Reviews of novels, 1876, 1886 (Box 24, Folder 608)
    - Scrapbook, undated (Box 24, Folder 609)
    - Scrapbook, undated (Box 25, Folder 610)
    - Scrapbook of poetry, undated (Box 25, Folder 611)
    - Sketchbook, undated (Box 25, Folder 612)
    - Travel brochures, undated (Box 25, Folder 613)
    - Writings, 1882-1891, undated (Box 25, Folder 614-618)
    - Writings, undated (Box 26, Folder 619)
  - Roe, Mary Wickham
    - Addresses, undated (Box 26, Folder 620)
    - China Information Service, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 621)
    - Financial records, 1907-1928 (Box 26, Folder 622-629)
    - Financial records: accounts, 1914-1938 (Box 26, Folder 630-631)
    - Financial records: estate, 1941-1943 (Box 26, Folder 632-634)
    - Friends of Spain, 1935-1937 (Box 26, Folder 635)
    - Genealogical records, 1921-1923 (Box 26, Folder 636)
    - Greeting cards, undated (Box 26, Folder 637)
    - Magazine fiction, undated (Box 26, Folder 638-639)
    - Marriage certificate, 1887 (Box 27, Folder 640)
    - Maps, undated (Box 27, Folder 641-643)
    - Mementos of Walter Clark Roe, undated (Box 27, Folder 644)
    - Memorabilia of European tour, 1902-1903 (Box 27, Folder 645)
    - Missionary certificate, Reformed Church in America, 1913 (Box 27, Folder 646)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1923-1940, undated (Box 27, Folder 647-649)
    - Newspaper clippings on speaking tours, undated (Box 27, Folder 650)
    - Notebooks, 1899, undated (Box 27, Folder 651-654)
    - Notebooks of poetry, undated (Box 27, Folder 655)
    - Notes, undated (Box 27, Folder 656)
    - Notes and clippings found in Bible, undated (Box 28, Folder 657)
    - Obituaries, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 658)
    - Pamphlets, undated (Box 28, Folder 659-661)
    - Papers, undated (Box 28, Folder 662)
    - Petition to Ft. Worth School Board, 1895 (Box 28, Folder 663)
    - Poetry, undated (Box 28, Folder 664-666)
    - School report, Cornwall Collegiate Institute, 1879 (Box 29, Folder 667)
  - Roe, Mary Wickham
    - South American trip, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 668-670)
    - Wedding invitation, 1887 (Box 28, Folder 671)
    - Writings, 1893, 1903, undated (Box 28, Folder 672-674)
    - Writings with Walter Clark Roe: Bible Stories, undated (Box 28, Folder 675-676)
    - Writings with Walter Clark Roe: Bible Stories, undated (Box 29, Folder 677-679)
  - Roe, Peter: obituaries, 1877 (Box 29, Folder 680)
  - Roe, Walter Clark
    - Biographical notes, 1911-1912 (Box 29, Folder 681)
    - Financial records, 1904-1913 (Box 29, Folder 682-684)
    - Lecture notes, undated (Box 29, Folder 685)
    - Ministerial licenses, 1892-1897 (Box 29, Folder 686)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 29, Folder 687)
    - Notes on the Bible, undated (Box 29, Folder 688)
    - Obituaries, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 689)
    - Pamphlets, undated (Box 29, Folder 690)
    - "Switzerland", undated (Box 29, Folder 691)
    - Writings, undated (Box 29, Folder 692)
  - Wickham family genealogy, undated (Box 29, Folder 693)
- Diaries, 1856-1960; Series III; 3.0' (7 boxes)
  Diaries and appointment books kept by various members of the Roe family are housed in Boxes 30-36. They have been arranged alphabetically by person and then chronologically.
  - Roe, Alfred Cox
    - Diaries, 1856-1870 (Box 30, Folder 694-699)
    - Diaries, 1871-1887 (Box 31, Folder 700-705)
    - Diaries, 1888-1900 (Box 32, Folder 706-710)
    - Memo books, undated (Box 32, Folder 711)
  - Roe, Joseph Wickham
    - Diaries, 1884-1927 (Box 33, Folder 712-718)
    - Office diary, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 719)
    - Diaries, 1928-1935 (Box 33, Folder 720-721)
    - Diaries, 1936-1960 (Box 34, Folder 722-728)
  - Roe, Mary Abigail
    - Diary, 1879 (Box 34, Folder 729)
  - Roe, Mary Wickham
    - Diary, 1877 (Box 34, Folder 730)
    - Journals of visits to Colony, 1891, 1896 (Box 34, Folder 731)
    - Journal at Colony, 1897-1900 (Box 34, Folder 732)
    - Reference diary, 1897-1911 (Box 35, Folder 733)
    - Diaries, 1898-1926 (Box 35, Folder 734-38)
    - Diaries, 1925-1928 (Box 36, Folder 739-740)
  - Roe, Walter Clark
    - Diaries, 1887-1909 (Box 36, Folder 741-747)
- Sermons, 1865-1911; Series IV; 3.5' (8 boxes)
  Series IV, SERMONS, fills Boxes 37-44 and contains sermons by Alfred Cox Roe and Walter Clark Roe. These have been arranged alphabetically by author and then chronologically.
  - Roe, Alfred Cox
    - "List of Selected Sermons", undated (Box 37, Folder 748)
    - Sermons, 1865-1871 April (Box 37, Folder 749-765)
    - Sermons, 1871 July-1872 June (Box 38, Folder 766-781)
    - Sermons, 1872 July-1873 December (Box 39, Folder 782-799)
    - Sermons, 1874 January-1875 June (Box 40, Folder 800-816)
    - Sermons, 1875 July-1879 August (Box 41, Folder 817-833)
    - Sermons, 1885-1898, undated (Box 42, Folder 834-843)
  - Roe, Walter Clark
    - "List of sermons", undated (Box 42, Folder 844)
    - Sermons 1-27, undated (Box 42, Folder 845-851)
    - Sermons 31-91, 1893-1895 (Box 43, Folder 852-867)
    - Sermons 92-163, 1896, undated (Box 44, Folder 868-878)
    - Mission sermons, 1904-1911 (Box 44, Folder 879)
    - Sermon fragments, undated (Box 44, Folder 880-881)
    - Sermon notes, undated (Box 44, Folder 882-884)
- Printed Works, 1849-1939; Series V; 5.25' (13 boxes)
  Series V, PRINTED WORKS, is housed in Boxes 45-57. Works by Roe family members have been placed first, arranged alphabetically by author and title. These are followed by Works by Others, arranged alphabetically by author, or by title in the case of anonymous works.
  - Works by Roe Family Members
    - Roe, Alfred Cox
      - Oral Lessons… in Latin, 1849 (Box 45, Folder 885)
    - Roe, Edward Payson (Box 45, Folder 885)
      - A of Fate, 1880 (Box 45, Folder 886)
      - A Day of Fate, 1902 (Box 45, Folder 887)
      - Driven Back to Eden, 1885 (Box 45, Folder 888)
      - The Earth Trembled, 1887 (Box 46, Folder 889)
      - A Face Illumined, 1878 (Box 46, Folder 890)
      - From Jest to Earnest, 1886 (Box 46, Folder 891)
      - He Fell in Love with His Wife, 1886 (Box 47, Folder 892)
      - His Sombre Rival, 1883 (Box 47, Folder 893)
      - The Home Acre, 1889 (Box 47, Folder 894)
      - A Knight of the Nineteenth Century, 1877 (Box 48, Folder 895)
      - Miss Lou, 1888 (Box 48, Folder 896)
      - Nature's Serial Story, 1902 (Box 48, Folder 897)
      - Near to Nature's Heart, 1876 (Box 49, Folder 898)
      - Opening a Chestnut Burr, 1885 (Box 49, Folder 899)
      - An Original Belle, 1885 (Box 49, Folder 900)
      - Play and Profit in My Garden, 1893 (Box 50, Folder 901)
      - Success with Small Fruits, 1881 (Box 50, Folder 902)
      - Taken Alive, 1892 (Box 50, Folder 903)
      - An Unexpected Result, 1883 (Box 50, Folder 904)
      - What Can She Do?, 1892 (Box 51, Folder 905)
      - What Can She Do?, 1902 (Box 51, Folder 906)
      - Without a Home, 1881 (Box 51, Folder 907)
      - A Young Girl's Wooing, 1902 (Box 51, Folder 908)
    - Roe, Joseph Wickham
      - Christian Activity at Yale, III, undated (Box 52, Folder 909)
      - Inventors and Engineers of Old New Haven, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 910)
      - Inventors and Engineers of Old New Haven, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 911)
      - James Hartness, 1937 (Box 52, Folder 912)
      - Yale Banner, Vol. LIII, 1894 (Box 52, Folder 913)
    - Roe, Mary Abigail
      General
      See also: box 162, folder 73
      - Left in the Wilderness, 1886 (Box 53, Folder 914)
      - A Long Search, 1885 (Box 53, Folder 915)
    - Roe, Mary E., The Count of Elsinore; or, Valdemar the Baltic Rover, 1901 (Box 53, Folder 916)
  - Works by Others
    - Army and Navy Service Book, 1918 (Box 53, Folder 917)
    - Bassi, Ugo, Sermon in the Hospital, 1888 (Box 53, Folder 918)
    - Bible (Roe, Mary Wickham), 1886 (Box 53, Folder 919)
    - Bible (Roe, Walter Clark), 1864 (Box 54, Folder 920)
    - Bible (Roe, Walter Clark), undated (Box 54, Folder 921)
    - Bible (New Testament only), undated (Box 54, Folder 922)
    - Bridgewater State Normal School. Teacher's Guides, 1894, undated (Box 54, Folder 923)
    - Burgess, Edward. Guide to the Student in Botany, 1887 (Box 54, Folder 924)
    - Carpenter, Frank C. Lands of the Caribbean, 1925 (Box 55, Folder 925)
    - Curious Cobwebs, 1884 (Box 55, Folder 926)
    - Dorchester, D. "Alfred Tennyson," "What Is Literature?" "What Is Poetry?", Undated 1893, 1892 (Box 55, Folder 927)
    - Ewing, Juliana Horatia. Mrs. Overtheway's Remembrances, 1893 (Box 55, Folder 928)
    - Farmer, Fannie. The Boston Cooking School Cookbook, 1918 (Box 55, Folder 929)
    - Ferson, May Lyon. The Legend of the Narrows in Geneva Lake, undated (Box 55, Folder 930)
    - Gospel of St. John, 1879 (Box 55, Folder 931)
    - Hauser Method of Harmonized Food Selections, undated (Box 56, Folder 932)
    - Hawes, Joel, Character Everything to the Young, 1892 (Box 56, Folder 933)
    - Hawthorne, Nathaniel. The Celestial Railroad, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 934)
    - Kellogg, H. and D. Indians of the Southwest, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 935)
    - Llwyd, J.P.D. The Message of an Indian Relic, 1909 (Box 56, Folder 936)
    - Luigi, A Legend of Lake Leman, 1885 (Box 56, Folder 937)
    - McLeod. Lessons on Common Minerals, 1891 (Box 56, Folder 938)
    - Miller System of Typewriting, 1919 (Box 56, Folder 939)
    - Reeve, James Knapp. 500 Places to Sell Manuscripts, 1900 (Box 56, Folder 940)
    - Schumacker, Anna, The Columbia Book of Yarns, 1906 (Box 56, Folder 941)
    - Selleck, Mrs. E.E. Dr. Selleck's Cookbook, undated (Box 56, Folder 942)
    - Snyder, Marcia Penfield. Eight Lands in Eight Weeks, 1911 (Box 56, Folder 943)
    - Soule and Campbell. Pronouncing Handbook, 1873 (Box 57, Folder 944)
    - We Drivers, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 945)
    - Woodhull, John F., Simple Experiments for the School Room, 1889 (Box 57, Folder 946)
    - Z.H.F. Typescript of articles, undated (Box 57, Folder 947)
- Family Photographs, 1861-1960; Series VI; 3.5' (9 boxes)
  Boxes 58-66 of the Roe Family Papers contain Series VI, FAMILY PHOTOGRAPHS. Boxes 58-63 contain alphabetically arranged pictures of people, while Boxes 64-65 contain pictures of places. Box 66 holds lantern slides.
  - Albee family, 1871-1874 (Box 58, Folder 948)
  - Allen, Leda, 1903 (Box 58, Folder 949)
  - Allison, Edward, and relatives, undated (Box 58, Folder 950)
  - Anderson family, undated (Box 58, Folder 951)
  - Burnham family, undated (Box 58, Folder 952)
  - Caldwell family, undated (Box 58, Folder 953)
  - Caldwell, Susan Elizabeth, 1886, undated (Box 58, Folder 954)
  - Clark family, undated (Box 58, Folder 955)
  - Cloud, Elizabeth Bender, undated (Box 58, Folder 956)
  - Cloud, Henry Roe, undated (Box 58, Folder 957)
  - Cox, Samuel, 1865, undated (Box 58, Folder 958)
  - Coy family, undated (Box 58, Folder 959)
  - Fisher family and Fitch family, undated (Box 58, Folder 960)
  - Hall family, undated (Box 58, Folder 961)
  - Hoffman, Maud, undated (Box 58, Folder 962)
  - Landon, Caroline Powell Roe, 1880, undated (Box 58, Folder 963)
  - Landon, Henry L., ("Dick")? (Box 58, Folder 964)
  - Lyman, Elizabeth Schauffler, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 965)
  - McMillan family, undated (Box 58, Folder 966)
  - Marvin family, undated (Box 58, Folder 967)
  - Merwin family, undated (Box 58, Folder 968-969)
  - Merwin, A. Moss, 1864 (Box 58, Folder 970)
  - Merwin, Miranda, undated (Box 58, Folder 971)
    See also: box 164, folder 78
  - Miscellaneous pictures and prints, undated (Box 58, Folder 972)
  - Page family, undated (Box 58, Folder 973)
  - Page, Alfred Rider, undated (Box 58, Folder 974)
  - Page, Elizabeth Merwin Roe, 1932, undated (Box 58, Folder 975)
  - Porter family, undated (Box 59, Folder 976)
  - Quinan family, 1884, undated (Box 59, Folder 977)
  - Roe family, 1874, 1893, undated (Box 59, Folder 978-980)
  - Roe family friends, undated (Box 59, Folder 981-982)
  - Roe, Alfred Cox, 1865, 1882, 1901, undated (Box 59, Folder 983-984)
    See also: box 114, folder 1973
  - Roe, Alfred Cox and Roe, Emma Wickham, 1900 (Box 59, Folder 985)
  - Roe, Alfred Cox - friends, 1864-1865 (Box 59, Folder 986)
  - Roe, Alfred Cox - University of the City of New York, class of 1843, 1893 (Box 59, Folder 987)
  - Roe, Caroline Clark, 1926, undated (Box 60, Folder 988)
  - Roe, Caroline Marsh, undated (Box 60, Folder 989)
  - Roe, Edward Payson and family, 1865, undated (Box 60, Folder 990)
  - Roe, Emma Wickham, 1861, 1872, 1884, 1901 (Box 60, Folder 991)